

Personal details



Hamza Rashed



hamza.rashed.sy@gmail.com



00962797596614



Jordan-Amman



hamzarashed.herokuapp.com



linkedin.com/in/hamzarashed-9864321b3



youtube.com/channel/UCS KljGf8al5Y7W5taSrkqOw



github.com/Hamza-Rashed

Technical Skills

Data Structure and Algorithms	••••
Object Oriented Programming	••••
JAVA	••••
Python	••••
Java Script	••••
Type Script	••••
Kotlin	••••
Node js	••••
React js	••••

Redux & Redux toolkit ••••

Play framework

Hamza Rashed

As a problem solver who loves facing challenges in my work, I'm excited to be at the deployment phase of my career as a web developer. I'm passionate and ambitious about my work, and love to be on a team that questions possibilities. I've previously been a Full stack developer, and bring those skills to my company . Independently, I've accomplished website building projects as a freelancer for over two years. Also as a trainer for many years .

Employment

Software Engineer

Jan 2020 - Mar 2022

eTip, USA

- Created functional web application and communicated with clients to identify their needs and requirements.
- Wrote code, resolved any problematic issues, and performed professional UI test to optimize performance.
- Trained and coordinated new personnel, maintained relevant correspondence, and worked closely with designers and system administrators.
- Recognized by the company executives as a top-achieving employee for successfully finishing all assigned projects and tasks within budget and schedule.

Back-End Developer

Jan 2019 - Jan 2021

freelance, Jordan

- Created functional web application and communicated with clients to identify their needs and requirements.
- Wrote code, resolved any problematic issues,
- Work on integration with Azure, Quickbooks using Node js

Programming Trainer

Mar 2018 - Feb 2019

CHAM Org, Turkey

Worked on training university students with their programmingrelated materials, and also worked on a number of graduation projects in different programming languages for them

ICDL Trainer

Feb 2015 - Jan 2021

NRC. Jordan

Trainning ICDL (International Computer Driving License) and ICDL Advanced which is from Specto.

Data Management Analyst

Feb 2018 - May 2020

BLUMONT, Jordan

Formulating management techniques for quality data collection to ensure adequacy, accuracy and legitimacy of data. Devising and implementing efficient and secure procedures for data management and analysis with attention to all technical aspects.

FreeLance Trainer

Oct 2021 - Dec 2021

FCA, Jordan

Training programming students on how to deal with freelance platforms such as (Mostaqel, Baeed, Khamsat, FreeLance, LinkedIn) and many others, ways to deal with the customer, how to work with

Django

PostgreSql

Mongodb

HTML, CSS, SASS

jQuery, bootstrab

Socket.io

NPM

JSON

Skills

Soft Skills

Communication Skills

Self Motivation

Time Management

Work under pressure

Teamwork

Adaptability

Creativity

Interpersonal Skills

Languages

Arabic

English

French

Hobbies

- Writing
- Cooking
- Reading
- Video Games
- Sports and Exercise
- Music

prices and budgets, and the difference between freelancing and entrepreneurship

Tools and Deployment

Git & GitHub & GitLab	•••••
VSCode	••••••
IntelliJ IDEA	••••••
AWS	••••••
Asure	•••••
Heroku	••••••
Windows, linux, Mac	••••••
Postman	•••••
Trello	•••••
Notion	•••••
Jira	•••••
Microsoft Office	•••••

Education

Advanced web development

Jan 2019 - Jan 2022

LTUC ASAC, Jordan

Deplom on Full stack web development. More advanced techniques in programming, Work in advanced way .Very intense study

IT Jan 2018 - Jan 2021

Al al-Bayt University, Jordan

How to create a complete website high quality using the latest technologies currently available .

Adding aesthetics to the site through animation and other modern techniques .

Volunteering

Trainer Strengthening Courses

Jan 2013 - Feb 2018

Work to train young people on several matters, including:

- Effective communication .
- Programming.
- · Mathematics and English.

Band aid

Jan 2017 - Dec 2017

- Assisting refugee patients with urgent cases through initial treatments until they are transported to the nearest hospital.
- Training new people on first aid.